(Sheldon:)Dear Lord, are you still going
to be here on French toast day?
(Penny:)Morning.
(Sheldon:)Look, Leonard,
Penny made French toast.
(Leonard:)Sorry, I haven't given her
your schedule yet.
(Sheldon:)It's an iCal download.
She can put it right in her phone.
And we agreed you'd have
conjugal visits in her apartment.
(Leonard:)We did, but there
were extenuating circumstances.
(Sheldon:)I see. Did her abysmal housekeeping
skills finally trump her perkiness?
No, her bed kind of broke.
(Sheldon:)That doesn't seem likely.
Her bed's of sturdy construction.
(Sheldon:)Even the addition
of a second normal-sized human...
...wouldn't cause a structural failure,
much less a homunculus such as yourself.
(Penny:)A homunculus?
(Leonard:)Perfectly formed miniature human being.
(Penny:)Oh, you're my little homunculus.
(Leonard:)Don't do that.